# JH / JACKSON HALL

igacksonthall22@gmail.com | € (802) 356-4622 | fm linkedin.com/in/jackson-t-hall | € github.com/jacksonthall22

gmail.com | € (802) 356-4622 | fm linkedin.com/in/jackson-t-hall | € github.com/jacksonthall22

## **SUMMARY**

Ambitious, quick learner with an acute attention to detail and an eye for design. Expert in Python with 10+ years' experience using it for personal and class projects. Practiced in Java, C++, and more (see: Skills). Started two businesses to help pay for college. Feel free to connect on <u>LinkedIn!</u>

#### **COURSES TAKEN**

[Computer Science] Intro to Web Site Dev • Intro to Programming: Python • Intermediate Programming: Java • Advanced Programming: C++ • Database Design for Web • Computer Organization • Operating Systems • Software Engineering • Computability & Complexity • Data Structures & Algorithms • [Math] Discrete Structures • Calculus I • Calculus II • Statistics for Engineering • Applied Probability • [In Progress] Algorithm Design & Analysis • Compiler Construction • Calculus III • Linear Algebra

#### **WORK HISTORY**

## Persimmon LLC - Founder & CEO

Thetford, Vermont • 06/2019 - 09/2020

- Curated a retail arbitrage storefront through Amazon's FBA program
- Conducted data-driven market analysis to determine profitability of potential products
- Built listings using keyword optimization techniques to improve SEO and maximize impressions in Amazon search results
- Purchased, priced, listed, packed, and shipped over 600+ items across 40+ SKUs
- Hired and trained one product sourcing agent, providing direct supervision and mentorship

### **Ecommerce Store – Founder & CEO**

Thetford, Vermont • 07/2019 - 01/2021

- Managed a store that capitalized on a political trend to offer an opportunity for frustrated Americans to support multiple charities with purchases of ecofriendly products
- Designed two products with quality in mind and oversaw all stages of production
- Efficiently outsourced talent and managed a family team to take brand from conception to launch on a four-month timeline
- Built relationships with international manufacturers and coordinated large shipments
- Designed, developed, and optimized storefront with Shopify's theme builder and Liquid language

## Project in C++: 4D Rendering Engine Sandbox

06/2019 – 12/2020 • This project began as a class assignment but grew into a 7000+ line program that I continued to develop out of personal interest. Written with C++ and using the FreeGLUT graphics API, the program launches a GUI that casts arbitrary 4D polytopes into 3D meshes, then into 2D points on the screen. The user toggles between a 3D and 4D camera that use velocity-based movement to navigate the scene. Technical details about the implementation can be read in the project's README on GitHub. I was especially proud of the result because I derived all math for perspective projection on my own and did not use any built-in matrix transforms traditionally relied upon in other 3D games. The project ended up winning first place at UVM's 2020 Computer Science Fair in its category.

## **EDUCATION**

## University of Vermont Honors College

Computer Science, B.S.

Graduating 05/2022

- Catamount Commitment Scholarship recipient
- Dean's ListFall 2018& Spring 2019
- Intramural soccer and other sports, Entrepreneurship Club, and co-founding Chess Club

## **Thefford Academy**

Thetford, VT 2018

- High Honors recipient for 12 semesters (max possible)
- Graduated in top decile

## **SKILLS**

- Technical: Python, C++, Java, HTML5, CSS, SQL, PHP, Git, Linux, Liquid, x86
- Other: Qiskit API, Mathematica, LaTeX, Blender
- Languages: Spanish (10yrs of study)